[
  {
    "question": "When searching for text in Word, which option shows results from the document and the internet?",
    "options": [
      "The find button in the editing section of the Home tab",
      "The navigation pane checkbox in the show section of the View tab",
      "The search bar at the top of the window",
      "The advanced find option accessed by clicking the arrow next to the Find button"
    ],
    "answer": "The search bar at the top of the window"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you copy and apply formatting to different text sections using the Format Painter?",
    "options": [
      "Right-click on the text and choose the Copy Format option",
      "Select the text and press Ctrl+C",
      "Click and drag the Format Painter across the desired text",
      "Select the text and press Ctrl+V"
    ],
    "answer": "Right-click on the text and choose the Copy Format option"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Excel Ribbon tab allows you to add PivotTables, Charts, and Illustrations?",
    "options": [
      "Home",
      "Data",
      "Insert",
      "Review"
    ],
    "answer": "Insert"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Microsoft Office feature helps automate a series of steps?",
    "options": [
      "Macros",
      "Formula Painter",
      "Formula Auditing",
      "Zoom"
    ],
    "answer": "Macros"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you customize the ribbon view in Outlook for a compact layout?",
    "options": [
      "Click on the reading pane",
      "Hover over the navigation pane",
      "Use the toggle switch on the status bar",
      "Click the arrow on the right side of the ribbon"
    ],
    "answer": "Click the arrow on the right side of the ribbon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which text formatting option can be applied to email messages in Outlook?",
    "options": [
      "Changing the email background to a picture.",
      "Adding animations to text.",
      "Changing font styles, colors, and highlighting.",
      "Embedding videos within the email."
    ],
    "answer": "Changing font styles, colors, and highlighting."
  },
  {
    "question": "What file type is created when you record a slide show in PowerPoint and select Save as Show?",
    "options": [
      ".ppt",
      ".ppts",
      ".ppsx",
      ".pptshow"
    ],
    "answer": ".ppsx"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you number a list with Roman numerals in PowerPoint to complement a Roman theme?",
    "options": [
      "Switch to a theme that supports Roman numerals",
      "Use photos of Roman numerals as bullet points",
      "Manually type Roman numerals next to list items",
      "Select the arrow next to Numbering and choose Roman numerals"
    ],
    "answer": "Select the arrow next to Numbering and choose Roman numerals"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can Gary join a Team Meeting in Microsoft Teams?",
    "options": [
      "Using his Outlook Calendar",
      "Using his Teams Calendar",
      "Using the link that takes him to Teams on the Web",
      "All of the Above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the Above"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Benjamin add a channel in the Employee Benefits team in Microsoft Teams?",
    "options": [
      "Employee Benefits > More Options > Add Channel",
      "Employee Benefits > More Options > Manage Team",
      "Employee Benefits > More Options > Manage Tags",
      "Employee Benefits > More Options > Edit Team"
    ],
    "answer": "Employee Benefits > More Options > Add Channel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where in Microsoft Teams would Gabriella set up an automatic reply for when she's out of the office?",
    "options": [
      "General Settings",
      "Notifications",
      "App Permissions",
      "Privacy"
    ],
    "answer": "General Settings"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Microsoft ask to keep you signed in when installing the Microsoft Teams Desktop app?",
    "options": [
      "Windows will automatically sign you in to your apps/websites",
      "Windows will keep you signed into this app only",
      "Windows will reduce the amount of times you are asked to log in",
      "Both A and C"
    ],
    "answer": "Both A and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Gilbert deleted a document in SharePoint, what did he find when he clicked the recycle bin?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing, deleted documents cannot be restored",
      "He found the deleted document and was able to restore it",
      "He found the deleted document, but could not restore it",
      "None of the Above"
    ],
    "answer": "He found the deleted document and was able to restore it"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Jasper save a filtered employee list in SharePoint for future use?",
    "options": [
      "After filtering, Click on Filter > Edit Current view > Name the view > Save",
      "You need to filter it every time you view the list",
      "After filtering, Click on All Items > Save view as > Name the view > Save",
      "He cannot save the filtered list"
    ],
    "answer": "After filtering, Click on All Items > Save view as > Name the view > Save"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is answering Facebook quizzes with personal information dangerous?",
    "options": [
      "You are helping potential hackers by giving them your personal information",
      "These questions could be security questions that give access to personal accounts",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the Above"
    ],
    "answer": "Both A and B"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the safest solution when using free Wi-Fi at a coffee shop?",
    "options": [
      "That's great! It's Free! Log on!",
      "Log on but avoid banking or personal information",
      "Use your own personal mobile hotspot",
      "None of the Above"
    ],
    "answer": "Use your own personal mobile hotspot"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for using cloud-based solutions outside of those provided by your company?",
    "options": [
      "Shadow IT",
      "BYOD",
      "HIPPA",
      "Microsoft 365"
    ],
    "answer": "Shadow IT"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most common starting point for cyber attacks?",
    "options": [
      "A USB drive in the parking lot",
      "A person impersonating a delivery or IT support person",
      "A phishing email",
      "A phone call"
    ],
    "answer": "A phishing email"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you compress multiple files into a zipped folder on Windows?",
    "options": [
      "Right-click on the files, select \"Send to\" > \"Compressed (zipped) folder\"",
      "Left-click on the files, select \"File\" > \"Compress\"",
      "Drag and drop the files into a pre-existing compressed folder",
      "Use the Windows Search bar to find the \"Compress Files\" tool"
    ],
    "answer": "Right-click on the files, select \"Send to\" > \"Compressed (zipped) folder\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the UK's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) regarding data protection?",
    "options": [
      "To provide internet services to the public.",
      "To collect data from individuals and organizations for government use.",
      "To uphold information rights, promote openness, and protect data privacy.",
      "To design data protection software for businesses and organizations."
    ],
    "answer": "To uphold information rights, promote openness, and protect data privacy."
  }
 ]